bro thank you for all the knowledge
thank you for how he knows you to go man
I just want to say thank you so much he
basically taught me everything and kept
me from quitting all right just flew in
from Dallas Texas here's some proof real
quick
through from DFW to Atlanta
and then from Atlanta to Miami just got
here at six he's giving me a lot of
momentum and to keep going not giving up
no matter what broker 21 see you at the
top there's a lot let us say I don't
think there's enough seats look for the
Traders and then let them in all right
so I don't know how we're gonna fit
everybody in here right now the capacity
is 300 people and the line went all the
way to the ocean Bank like outside of
the school so I don't know how everybody
do this right now
foreign
[Music]
so I just got home right now because I
was literally escorted out on the campus
Because he told me if I didn't leave the
premises I was gonna get arrested
because I was causing commotion or crowd
whatever they told me really said that
if I stayed on the campus longer than 10
minutes they were gonna arrest me I'm so
sorry to all of you guys that pulled up
I know there's a lot of people that
drove 10 15 hours people flew out from
Texas to come to the event flew out from
Puerto Rico I'm so sorry that I wasn't
able to make this happen I will make up
for it for you guys stay tuned to the
next video because I'm going to make the
next one 10 times bigger and I'm going
to give back 10 times more than what I
was originally gonna give back this time
so with that being said Thank you every
single person that pulled to the event
those of you that waited in the line for
hours there was people there since five
o'clock in the afternoon and the event
started at eight o'clock so big thank
you to all of you guys that pulled up
for those of you guys that couldn't get
in I couldn't get that one-on-one
connection with you guys I apologize
I'll make sure from this point forward
the logistics is 100 ready I did not
expect the fan base and the energy to be
this crazy so I apologize guys but I
will make up for it
Forex millionaire Trader yeah
yeah
they're UPS was it down
was there UPS was there Downs
this is how I did it so everything
started here in this very Auditorium
this is where I got recruited to a
multi-level marketing in that seat right
there because these social media gurus
these multi-level marketers they would
fill up this whole entire Auditorium of
just people selling them the dream that
they're going to teach them how to be a
Forex Trader teach them how they're
going to give them a strategy and I was
one of those guys that I felt victim in
that very seat right there about five
years ago so after being here watching
their for like two months I realized
what they're selling is just air they're
just telling you how to become part of a
multi-level marketing pyramid not
teaching you anything I'll give them a
little bit of credit because if they're
not been for them I don't not even know
what Forex is but it was in this very
spot where my Forex Journey started so
like many of you guys I had a job I
worked here at Duncan like many of you
guys may know so as I'm in in this
multi-level marketing trying to figure
out how I'm gonna sell people these
people would literally tell me get on
your phone call 100 people and tell to
come to our next event and I'm like yo
that's not how you learn how to trade
but as I'm doing that I'm here working
this job every single week I'm
depositing the hundred dollars I made in
the week into my trading account blowing
it depositing again next week blowing it
and so probably I say about 15 20
accounts that I blew I finally was able
to flip a hundred dollar account 150
account to a 1500 account I'm like yo
this is it this is literally going to be
what's going to be the change and
obviously I blew that account as well
because just I wasn't using risk
management wasn't using any of that
stuff so like many of you guys I was
learning how to trade and I had a job at
the same time so there's no excuses as
to why you shouldn't be learning how to
trade but before I got my biggest payout
like many of you guys as I'm working my
job I am watching YouTube videos day in
and day out in a little closet in my
parents house right this is obviously
not the closet uh but it's assimilated
because it's obviously a closet in my
house now but to show you guys the size
of it it wasn't always fancy big office
multiple computer screens I have this
old computer which is I still have the
same exact MacBook uh air the one that I
started trading with I keep it as like a
memory like a trophy because this is
where I learned everything you don't
need a fancy computer you don't need a
huge setup monitors all that stuff
you just need to have the consistency
the willing to put in the hours every
single night to succeed you don't need
to fancy anything I started off in a
closet like this with a dream working at
Duncan and it's just consist so the
story is full but how do you actually
get to a million yeah well probably
about about a year and a half of blowing
my own money in the markets I say I
probably lost about like twenty thirty
thousand dollars of my own capital in
the markets for about a year and a half
I came across funding companies I don't
want to say I was the pioneer of coming
across funding companies but I bought my
first challenge in 2019 ending of 2019.
so I've been dealing with this whole
funded account this whole challenge
thing for pretty much the majority of my
career I wouldn't be where I am today if
it wouldn't be for that funded account
right so my first funded account was a
100K Challenge and I ended up making
about 38 within the month I just had a
really nice winning streak and I got my
first payout and I'm not even gonna lie
I thought I was not gonna get paid out
but once the money hit my bank account I
got about a 28 30 000 check obviously
after the profit split at the time the
platform that I was using they gave me a
70 profit split when that money hit my
bank account like what
this is real after that I left my job
because I literally made enough money to
pay for my monthly expenses for a whole
entire year obviously the time we're
gonna done it I Duncan I had no expenses
it literally was just my car and my
lifestyle so once I realized that you
can actually make money with a funded
account you could actually make money
trading that is where everything
completely shifted so after I got that
thirty thousand dollar payout twenty
thousand dollar payout obviously I blew
my challenge account so yes the I was
funded got my first payout and then I
blew it but I did it again so I bought a
new challenge but this time I did
something different and I documented my
journey passing this challenge getting
funded and then getting my next payout
again you guys can go down in my YouTube
channel and see the videos I documented
everything and this is where I started
growing you guys a community the family
what you guys did was completely change
my life because those nights that I was
lazy those nights that I didn't want to
follow my trading plan or simply just
get a little bit loose and not follow my
rules you guys were there I mean hey why
aren't you doing this this if you told
me to do it and I'm like you know what
bro you're right I'm not leading by
example
and then how am I going to tell you to
do something if I personally can't do it
myself so what that did is forced me to
stay on my a game and that completely
shifted my trading because how am I
going to tell you to do something and I
personally can't do it myself so without
that type of accountability I would have
probably not been at this point right
now so I encourage every single one of
you guys get a trading buddy join my
free telegram join the rocket Discord
they're literally people in there that
are going to hold you accountable when
you can't do it because that is going to
be the difference it's going to be nice
where you get lazy and you just want to
click a button it's going to be somebody
else there that has a sharper mind so
then you'll be like hey don't do that
stick to your trading plus and that's
going to make the difference it's where
consistency in the right way versus
consistency in the wrong way so around
this time of my journey I'm managing
about 300K funded and I'm managing about
150k personal account so I can average
anywhere from seven to fifteen percent
on my funded account and you could
basically double that on my personal
account because there's no rules there I
could do whatever I want which is good
and bad because I can have much more
higher returns but the bad thing is when
I go into the draw that I can go into 25
30 35 drawdown of my personal account so
the longest I've held my funded account
was probably for about six months I
failed it enter a losing streak it
happens anybody out there that gets
funded and they tell you they don't lose
the account it is Cap Traders we're
going to enter losing streaks and it is
inevitable to know when it stops so I've
lost my funded account probably two
three times and then after that I now
joined rocket and then rocket has scaled
me to a million dollars so I was gonna
be a deal with rocket where they were I
was like oh if I bring my community to
you guys you guys give me a million
dollars and I'm and they're like okay
but let's do it but I'm like before I
bring the community to you guys I want
to make sure you guys are legit so I got
a 250 000 account I mean a 200 000
account and I scaled it to 250 000 I
mean 25 in three weeks they saw those
results they tripped up so I'm like all
right scale me to a million and is
coming to a million I'll bring my whole
entire Community to you guys so they
scaled me up to a half a million dollar
account the half million dollar account
I killed it and now they have officially
funded me a full million dollars so this
is where I want to say a big big big
thank you to every single one of you
guys out there because if I didn't have
the community I wouldn't have the
opportunity to go to a funding company
and ask them to give me a special deal
like they have but thanks to you guys
making me uh you know have all of this
influence I am able to go to them I'm
able to come back to you guys and make
sure you guys to go get funded at the
best possible platform ever there's no
other funding company out there there's
no other Trader out there that I've seen
with a million dollar account funded and
I'm going to show you guys how I'm going
to scale it from a mill hopefully up to
maybe 20 30 and they say if I leave a
certain Reserve they can scale me up to
two million dollars that's their cap
nursing any other Trader do it never
seen any other Guru do it so I'm doing
it for you guys showing you guys that if
I'm able to do it so can you you guys
and I want to make sure you guys are
part of the best Funding Company
Community they have just go to the
Discord go to their website go to
everything they have and you guys can
literally see they are Community Based I
want to say hit the Subscribe button at
100K we got a bigger giveaway coming
than this one and again if you guys
visualize yourself somewhere along in
the journey that you guys just saw I did
to scale now to where I'm at the million
just keep going consistency is key
without that it is not going to happen
nobody's going to come to you and tell
you you're going to be successful a
month from now you're going to be
successful a week from now there's no
countdown there's no specific day when
your consistency is going to come your
journey is going to go from this to then
about break even and then you'll start
heading to the upset it's not going to
have a sharp turn and now you're going
to be driving Lambos that's just not how
it works that's just not how life works
it wouldn't be fair to me would it be
fair to the people out there that put in
the work to succeed so again appreciate
you guys watching the video I'm going to
scale this rocket account to the moon
and I'll see you guys in video